#### **DMYTRO POLIULIUK**

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER



#### Contact details

Phone:

+38 (063) 518 14 29

Email:

dpoliuliuk@gmail.com

Skype:

dmytro071187

Date of birth:

Location: Kyiv, Ukraine

# Summary

About 2,5 years in cross-browser web-sites development (valid and responsive) With using HTML5, CSS3/SVG animations, SASS, jQuery and Vanilla JS, PHP Good communication and project negotiation skills, good team player Quick-learner with ability to share new knowledge with colleagues Cooperative, responsible, open-minded and self-motivated person



#### Technical Skills

- HTML/HTML5/CSS/CSS3/SASS/Flexboxes
- Vanilla JS, ES6, jQuery, Ajax, JSON, React JS, Redux, Jest, Bootstrap, Php Essential, SVG
- GIT, Gulp, Webpack, Bower, Npm, Yarn
- Avocode, Adobe Photoshop
- JIRA, Redmine, Scrum
- English, Italian

## Experience

Company: Nadavi Trade Systems (nadavi.net)

Period: Sep 2017 - Jan 2018
Position: Web-developer

Responsibilities: Support and expansion of the existing high-loaded trading platforms of

the company, development of admin panels, bug fixing

Technologies: HTML, CSS, jQuery, Vanilla JS, Underscore.js, Require.js, Git, Php

Products: ek.ua | m.ua | nadavi.com

Company: Hexa LLC (hexa.com)
Period: Aug 2016 – Sep 2017

Position: Middle Frontend web-developer

Responsibilities: Development web-sites, admin panel (app.essaypartner.com)
Technologies: HTML5, SASS/CSS3, jQuery, Vanilla JS, Gulp, Git, Scrum, PHP

Company: Web-studio Ship4web (ship4web.com)

Period: Jan 2016 - July 2016

Position: Junior Frontend web-developer
Responsibilities: Support and development web sites

Technologies: HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3, jQuery, WordPress

## Education

University: Kyiv National Transport University

Period: 2005 – 2010

Qualifications: Automotive engines

Degree: Master's Degree

Course: GoIT

Period: Aug-Dec 2015

Qualifications: Frontend-end Development

Course: Be Smart Community

Period: 2015 Subject: English

## Some Projects

Adaptive and responsive sites

custompaperhelp.com domyhomework123.com 123dissertation.com dissertationteam.com paperwritten.com vivaessays.com myhomeworkdone.com writemyessayz.com writemyessayz.com assignmentsavior.com mypaperwriting.com

Game

Game - GunMan

ezdissertation.com

React/Redux apps ca

cards.com mobshop.com chat with react/redux/websockets \*

 $^{\ast}$  as it works with custom server side, to see this project, you should clone it from github repository and follow the

Readme.md instructions

Dmytro Poliuliuk CV 2018